Guide to the Reston Association records, 1964-2006
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 3: Minutes, 1972-2004; (7 boxes)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    425.34
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    425.39
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    425.41
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    425.42
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    425.45
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    425.46
  - Board of Directors Budget Committee Meeting Minutes, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    425.47
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    425.49
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    425.51
  - Board of Directors Council Budget Meeting, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    424.26
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    425.30
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    425.23
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    425.25
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    425.28
  - Board of Directors Executive Session Minutes, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    425.29
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    425.20
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    425.21
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    425.16
  - Board of Directors Executive Session Meeting Minutes, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    425.18
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    425.14
  - Board of Directors Annual Meeting Minutes, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    425.10
  - Board of Directors and Council Meeting Minutes, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    425.5
  - Board of Directors and Council Special Meeting Minutes, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    425.6
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    425.7
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes Executive Session, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    425.27
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    424.28
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    425.1
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    424.25
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    424.20
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes Executive Session, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    424.21
  - Board of Directors and Reston Homeowner Association Meeting Minutes, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    424.22
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes-Special Meeting, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    424.23
  - Board of Directors And Reston Internal Bus System, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    424.15
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    424.16
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    424.17
  - Board of Directors Annual Meeting Minutes, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    424.11
  - Board of Directors Annual Meeting Minutes Executive Session, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    424.12
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    424.7
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    424.8
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    424.1
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    424.2
  - Board of Directors, 1968-1977 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    529.16
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1976-1994 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    529.17
  - Board of Directors Meeting Agendas, 1976-1993 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    529.15
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    17.14
  - Board Meeting and Notes, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    537.7
  - Board Meeting, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    528.14
  - Board Meeting, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    528.15
  - Board Meeting, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    528.16
  - Board Meeting, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    528.17
  - Board Meeting, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    528.19
  - Board Meeting, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    518.20
  - Board Meeting, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    528.21
  - Board Meeting, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    528.22
  - Board Meeting, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    528.23
  - Citizens Committee on Land Use and Transportation, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    427.17
  - Council Minutes, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    425.22
  - Council Meeting Minutes, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    425.19
  - Council Minutes, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    425.11
  - Council Minutes, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    425.13
  - Council Meeting, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    425.2
  - Council Meeting Minutes, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    425.3
  - Council Minutes, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    424.18
  - Council Minutes, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    424.19
  - Council Minutes, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    424.13
  - Council Minutes, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    424.14
  - Council Minutes, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    424.9
  - Council Minutes, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    424.4
  - Excerpt of Council Minutes, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    424.6
  - Facilities Advisory Committee, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    426.11
  - Facilities Advisory Committee, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    426.7
  - Facilities Advisory Committee Minutes, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    425.40
  - Facilities Advisory Committee Minutes, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    425.35
  - Facilities Task Force Minutes, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    425.15
  - Facilities Task Force Meeting Minutes, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    425.4
  - Facilities Task Force Minutes, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    424.24
  - Fiscal Committee, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    428.18
  - Fiscal Committee Minutes, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    428.9
  - Fiscal Committee, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    428.5
  - Lakes Ecology Advisory Committee, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    426.10
  - Lakes Ecology Advisory Committee, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    426.8
  - Lakes Ecology Advisory Committee and Natural Areas Advisory Committee, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    426.1
  - Meeting Agenda: Special Committee on Governing Documents Review, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    1.7
  - Meeting Agenda: Special Committee on Governing Documents Review, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    1.6
  - Minutes, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    437.14
  - Minutes of the Annual Meeting of the Members, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    425.9
  - Minutes of Annual Meeting of Members, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    424.10
  - Minutes of the Annual Meeting of Members, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    424.3
  - Minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    527.34
  - Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    527.35
  - Minutes, 19841 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    530.10
  - Minutes, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    530.11
  - Minutes, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    530.15
  - Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    521.5
  - Minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    526.2
  - Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    526.6
  - Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    526.5
  - Minutes, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    526.4
  - Minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    526.3
  - Personnel Committee, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    428.33
  - Personnel Committee Meeting Minutes, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    425.44
  - Personnel Committee Meeting Minutes, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    425.38
  - Planning and Zoning Minutes, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    527.28
  - Planning and Zoning Minutes, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    527.27
  - Political Meetings and Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    525.11
  - Political Meetings and Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    525.2
  - Programs and Plus Services Advisory Committee, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    426.3
  - Public Hearing, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    426.23
  - Public Safety, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    527.19
  - Recreation Services Advisory Committee, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    428.7
  - Reston Homeowners Association Natural Areas Advisory Committee, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    509.21
  - Reston Homeowners Association Lakes Ecology Advisory Committee, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    509.25
- Series 4: Reports, 1962-2005; (7 boxes)
  The Report Series includes 41 folders. The information dates from 1962 to 2005. The paperwork is information submitted to different organization within Reston, such as the council and the RHOA Board. The reports provided the associations with updates and information on various projects and programs within Reston such as land use. Also included in the series are the RHOA Plus White Papers from March of 1981.
  - A Study Group Proposal for the Formation of a Reston Community Association and Reston Community Association Interim Bylaws, 1970s (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - A Study Group Proposal for the Formation of a Reston Community Association, undated; 1.
  - A Tennis Enclosure for Reston-Report to the Board, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    17.16
  - Accountant's Report, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    10.3
  - Annual Report, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    506.6
  - Annual Report and Handbook, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    544.10
  - Annual Report-Documents Review Committee, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    425.8
  - Articles of Incorporation, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    535.10
  - Articles of Incorporation of Reston First Homeowners Association, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    1.9
    - Articals of Incorporation of Reston First Home Owners Association, August 8, 1966; 1.
  - Blue Ribbon Panel to Review Reston Association Assessment Cap-Report to Board of Directors, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    17.10
  - Board Administration, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    16.23
  - Board of Directors and Officers, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    425.48
  - Board of Directors-Personnel Committee, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    425.17
  - Board of Directors-Miscellaneous Issues, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    434.3
  - Board of Directors-Miscellaneous Issues, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    434.1
  - Board of Directors-Miscellaneous Issues, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    434.2
  - Booze and Allen Study, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    500.6
  - Building Today for a Strong Tomorrow-Reston Association Board Orientation, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    17.13
  - Bylaws of Reston First Homeowners Association, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    1.10
  - Bylaws, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    524.4
  - Capital Improvements, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    16.01
  - Commission on the Future (Prince William County 2010), 1990 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    537.5
  - Common Areas, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    17.02
  - Communication with Members, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    509.10
  - Community Preferences-A Follow-Up Study to the 1994 Shopper and Homeowner Survey and the 1995 New Urbanism Study, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    506.3
  - Community Organization Projects, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    509.12
  - Comprehensive Plan, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    524.2
  - Council, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    425.12
  - County Campaign, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    437.8
  - Covenants, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    17.01
  - Creppen-Lewis, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    524.1
  - Declaration of Covenants, Conditions and Restrictions for Reston Residential Center, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    440.8
  - Declaration of Covenants, Conditions and Restrictions for Reston Residential Center, 1990s (Box 15, Folder 6)
    440.7
  - Deed of Declaration of Protective Covenants and Restrictions, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    439.10
  - Drafts of Governing Documents/ Draft Revised Deed of Dedication of Reston, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    16.21
  - Executive Director-Annual Report, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    1.04
  - Fact Sheet-Small Tax District 5, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    16.13
  - Fairfax County Comprehensive Land Use Plan Adopted-June 30, 1975; Amended through June 26,1995 (Map) (Box 15, Folder 11)
    16.12
  - Fairfax County-Proposed Elements of a Program for Management of Traffic and Growth, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    536.15
  - Festival Survey Questionnaires, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    535.11
  - Final Report of the Reston Homeowners Association/Reston Community Association Land Use Committee Submitted to Reston Community Association Board and the Reston Homeowners Association Board, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    528.3
  - Final Report Submitted to Reston Community Association Board and the Reston Homeowners Association Board by Reston Homeowners Association/Reston Community Association Land Use Committee, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    528.2
  - Financial and Management Evaluation Draft Report, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    441.1
  - Financial and Management Evaluation Draft Report, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    441.2
  - Financial and Management Evaluation Draft Report, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    441.3
  - Financial and Management Evaluation Study Report, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    441.4
  - Financial and Management Evaluation Study Report, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    441.5
  - Financial and Management Evaluation Study Report, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    441.6
  - Financial and Management Evaluation Study Report, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    441.7
  - Gold Plus Market Research Survey, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    434.9
  - Governance, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    526.14a
  - Governance, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    526.14b
  - Governing Documents Review-Internal Analysis, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    1.4
  - Governing Documents Review-Internal Analysis, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    1.3
  - Governing Documents Review-Internal Analysis, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Governing Documents, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    16.22
  - Gulf Reston, Incorporated Position-Homeowners Association Consolidation, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    1.01
  - Homeless, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Index, 1990s (Box 17, Folder 6)
    17.04
  - Information Concerning Ridge Heights Pool Bubble, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    17.12
  - Lakeowners, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    437.5
  - Lakes Ecology Advisory Committee, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    425.37
  - Lake Study, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    437.4
  - Land Use Committee, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    436.4
    - Report: RHOA and RCA Task Force, May 1984; 1.
  - Land Use Committee, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    436.5
  - Land Use Planning/Community Development Revitalization, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    16.03
  - Magazines, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    534.6
  - Members of the Virginia Commission on Local Government, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    535.12
  - Miscellaneous Reports, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    534.1
    - Paper: John T. Dockery, "Tactical Considerations for 'New Towns' Citizens Groups: An Urban Guerilla Warfare Manual", undated; 1.
    - Report: Gulf Reston, Inc., "Reston, Virginia: Its Social Impact on Fairfax County", July 1973; 2.
    - Report: Reston Community Association Governance Committee, "The Advantages and Disadvantages of the Incorporation of Reston as a Town", September 1, 1978; 3.
  - Miscellaneous Reports, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    534.2
  - Miscellaneous Reports, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    17.03
  - New Towns in the United States, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    534.3
  - New Towns in the United States, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    534.4
  - New Towns in the United States, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    534.5
  - Office Reports, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    527.29
  - Park Authority Survey, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    535.14
  - Pathways Advisory Committee, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    426.28
  - Pathways Advisory Committee, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    425.43
  - Pathways, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    527.22
  - Personnel Committee, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    425.26
  - Plan for North Point Village Center and Reston Community Center, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    537.4
  - Report to Reston Homeowners Association (RHOA) for Quarter I, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    509.36
  - Reston Community Association Reports, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    530.3
  - Reston Community Association Reports, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    530.8
  - Reston 5-Year Strategic Computer Systems Plan, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    439.6
  - Reston Government Board, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    509.1
  - Reston Homeowners Association Meeting, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    509.33
  - Reston Homeowners Association (RHOA) Plus White Paper, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    436.1
  - Reston Homeowners Association (RHOA) Plus, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    436.2
  - Salary Benefits, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    441.8
  - Sheraton Inn Redevelopment, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    537.1
  - Shopper and Homeowner Survey of 1994, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    506.4
  - Special Meeting of Membership, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    425.24
  - St. John Newman, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    527.11
  - Streetlights, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    527.6
  - Streetlights, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    527.9
  - Survey, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    438.4
  - Survey, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    440.14
    - Comments on R-A Survey, November 10, 1988; 1.
  - Thoburn, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    527.4
  - Toward New Town Governance: The report of the Study Team on Reston Homeowners Association Role and Structure, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    1.03
  - Town Green, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    527.3
  - Treasurer's Report, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    529.10
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    529.11
  - United States Geological Survey, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    535.4
  - Zoning, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    536.8
- Series 5: Budget, 1969-1995; (5 boxes)
  There are 78 folders involving the Reston Association budget. The folders are dated from 1969 to 1995. The information involves the organization of the budget for various projects and programs such as the council individual budget and recreational programs. The information also includes assessments of the budget from various months during the 1980s and 1990s.
  - Appendices, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    509.15
  - Assessments Receivable, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Annual Operating Budget, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    438.2
  - Biennial Budgeting Report, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    431.9
  - Biennial Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    432.6
  - Biennial Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    432.5
  - Biennial Working Draft Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    431.8
  - Biennial Working Draft Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    431.7
  - Biennial Working Draft Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    431.6
  - Budget, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    429.2
  - Budget, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    429.8
  - Budgets, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    506.16
  - Budget Committee, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    509.31
  - Budget, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    429.9
  - Budget, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    429.10
  - Budget-Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    433.9
  - Budget-Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    433.10
  - Budget, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    430.6
  - Budget, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    430.5
  - Budget, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    430.7
  - Budget, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    430.8
  - Budget, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    509.14
  - Budget Markup Session, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    427.38
  - Budget Work Session, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    433.3
  - Budget Work Session, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    433.4
  - Budget Work Session, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    433.5
  - Budget Work Session, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    433.6
  - Budget Work Session, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    433.7
  - Budget Work Session, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    433.8
  - Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    432.7
  - Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    433.1
  - Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    433.2
  - Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    432.10
  - Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    432.11
  - Budget, 1970s (Box 22, Folder 5)
    1.06
  - Capital, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    509.9
  - Capital Budget, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    509.3
  - Cash Flow, 1987-1990 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    427.25
  - Community Projects, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    437.7
  - Comparative Income and Expenses, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    433.12
  - Corporation and Board, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Cost Estimates and Space Planning for Reston Community Center at Lake Anne, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    16.15
  - Council Budget Hearing, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Documents, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    439.8
  - Draft Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    432.2
  - Draft Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    432.1
  - Fairfax County Budget, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    528.13
  - Financial Reports, 1970s (Box 22, Folder 18)
    1.05
  - Financial Services, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Financial Statements, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    430.3
  - Financial Statements and Schedule, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    1.11
  - Financial Statements and Schedule, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Financial Statements, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    1.09
  - Financial Statements, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    430.9
  - Financial Statements, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    1.08
  - Financial Statements, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    431.3
  - Financial Statements, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    1.07
  - Fiscal Policies, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    16.24
  - Five Year-Long Range Plan, 1988-1993 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    432.4
  - Five Year-Long Range Plan, 1988-1993 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    432.3
  - Fund Statement-Current Spending to Operate Existing RCC Facility, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    16.18
  - Income, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    442.9
  - Income and Expenses, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    433.11
  - Income and Expenses, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    433.13
  - Income and Expenses, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    433.14
  - Individual Program Area Budget, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    509.5
  - Informational Round Table, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    526.11
  - Insurance and Bonds, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    526.9
  - Island Walk, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    526.10
  - Issues, 1980s (Box 23, Folder 16)
    437.1
  - Kaiser, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    509.4
  - Notes on Creating and Sustaining a RCC Financed Center on Lake Anne Plaza, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    16.16
  - Open Space, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    509.13
  - Program Budget, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    431.2
  - Program Budget, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    431.1
  - Program Budget, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    430.4
  - Program Budget, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    429.6
  - Program Budget, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    429.7
  - Program Budget, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Program Budget Summary, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    509.6
  - Recommended Accounting Adjustments for Reston Association, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    17.21
  - Report on Trade Study of Financial Services, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    431.10
  - Salary Structure, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    509.28
  - Summary Report of the Budget Document Review Task Force, 1990s (Box 25, Folder 4)
    440.2
  - Working Budget, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    432.8
  - Working Budget, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    432.9
  - Working Draft Budget, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    431.4
  - Working Draft Budget, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    431.5
  - Working Draft Budget, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    430.1
  - Working Draft Budget, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    430.2
  - Working Draft Budget, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    429.4
  - Working Draft Budget, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    429.5
  - Working Draft Budget, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    429.3
- Series 6: Committee, 1969-2000; (2 boxes)
  Series 6 is consists of paperwork from different Reston committees. Subjects that this series covers includes education, elections, health care and other issues. Also included is information from planning and zoning of Reston.
  - Becoming a Town, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    524.6
  - Becoming a Town, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    521.3
  - Becoming a Town, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    521.2
  - Becoming a Town, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    521.1